<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/</link><description>Recent content on rktpi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:48:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Web Service with NGINX</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/web/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/web/</guid><description>NGINX will be our web server RktPi uses nginx as it&amp;rsquo;s static content server and reverse proxy
rktpi will use the package distributed with raspbian
Installation and Base Config Part of the rktpi ansible deployment for nginx.
Nginx as Static Site Server for now, all paths are either open to the public or only for the owner of the device
every app has
public/// private/// private is a seperate server which only listens on 127</description></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/docs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/docs/</guid><description>Documentation is generated using Hugo. Using the package provided by raspbian apt.
Running Hugo from within the docs/ directory should build everything.
There is a CI Task which generates the site and deploys to gh-pages on each commit to main</description></item><item><title>Artboard</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/artboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:21:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/artboard/</guid><description>spray circles at the canvas
add some saturation
no overlap
rotate repeat (too many objects)
zoom, more r and r, new colors
Inspired by Amanda Hodges
https://github.com/thetanil/svg_play/blob/master/circle_wiggle_path.py
https://www.creativebloq.com/how-to/add-animation-to-svg-with-css
https://github.com/birjolaxew/svglint</description></item><item><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</guid><description>What it is A platform for web apps running on YOUR Pi, with YOUR Data, accessible from YOUR phone.
Your data in your home. Your safe space near the Internet.
Features A guard computer for your phone A transformer of documents An internet filtered of garbage A path out of the cloud Keep your own email, back it up EZ UX - just for you ads be damned Extremely opinionated to favor accessibility and UX performance No JS, just enough CSS to unify browsers, there is no ad network No colors, user theme-able viewer Gemini with markdown and pictures Target 3G full page renders under 200ms (not including images) Has to may may but with SVG they can be big think HighQualityGifs you see them when they are cached already comments about a content item are found in matrix via #content_id The Questions Rocket Pi is an attempt to answer the following questions:</description></item><item><title>CI (continuous integration)</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:29:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</guid><description>The rktpi as an end user product is heavily integrated into the CI system
this is only a first step to keep things simple. beta testers and developers should share an environment as much as possible
the end user will configure a GH repo for their Raspberry Pi, and they will run our GH Actions to bring their Pi into a working state for their own configuration.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/imprint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/imprint/</guid><description>Contact Theta Nil LLC thetanil@thetanil.com
+1 800 555 1212</description></item><item><title/><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>