<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/</link><description>Recent content on rktpi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</guid><description>What it is A guard computer for your phone A translator of documents An Internet presented as you asked A path out of the cloud The Questions Rocket Pi is an attempt to answer the following questions:
how can we get developers to build web apps which allow you to keep your data how can i legally show you your FB feed without all the garbage you didn&amp;rsquo;t ever ask for why can&amp;rsquo;t we have just email we can trust (spoiler: we can) many people want out of the cloud, but do not know how</description></item><item><title>CI (continuous integration)</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:29:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</guid><description>The rktpi as an end user product is heavily integrated into the CI system
this is only a first step to keep things simple. beta testers and developers should share an environment as much as possible
the end user will configure a GH repo for their Raspberry Pi, and they will run our GH Actions to bring their Pi into a working state for their own configuration.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/imprint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/imprint/</guid><description>Contact Theta Nil LLC thetanil@thetanil.com
+1 800 555 1212</description></item><item><title/><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>