<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on rktpi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</guid><description>What it is A platform for web apps running on YOUR Pi, with YOUR Data, accessible from YOUR phone.
Your data in your home. Your safe space near the Internet.
Features A guard computer for your phone A translator of documents An internet filtered of garbage A path out of the cloud Keep your own email, back it up EZ UX - just for you ads be damned Extremely opinionated to favor accessibility and UX performance No JS, just enough CSS to unify browsers, there is no ad network No colors, user theme-able viewer Gemini with markdown and pictures Has to may may but with SVG they can be big think HighQualityGifs you see them when they are cached already comments about a content item are found in matrix via #content_id The Questions Rocket Pi is an attempt to answer the following questions:</description></item><item><title>CI (continuous integration)</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 15:29:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/ci/</guid><description>The rktpi as an end user product is heavily integrated into the CI system
this is only a first step to keep things simple. beta testers and developers should share an environment as much as possible
the end user will configure a GH repo for their Raspberry Pi, and they will run our GH Actions to bring their Pi into a working state for their own configuration.</description></item></channel></rss>