<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>themes on rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/categories/themes/</link><description>Recent content in themes on rktpi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:21:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/categories/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/docs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/docs/</guid><description>Documentation is generated using Hugo. Using the package provided by raspbian apt.
Running Hugo from within the docs/ directory should build everything.
There is a CI Task which generates the site and deploys to gh-pages on each commit to main</description></item><item><title>Celery</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/celery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/celery/</guid><description>Celery and RabbitMQ Server are installed by the CI script.
A set of test tasks will generate a thorough test to excersise the system on each startup
This should give a good target for baseline utilization. Redis is still on the table as a broker and store. amqp and rpc are used now as recommended in the celery docs.
currently add task is working from demo need to deploy a systemd script to start celery and rabbitmq server.</description></item><item><title>Artboard</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/artboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:21:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/artboard/</guid><description>https://github.com/thetanil/svg_play/blob/master/circle_wiggle_path.py
https://www.creativebloq.com/how-to/add-animation-to-svg-with-css
https://github.com/birjolaxew/svglint
https://github.com/hogesonline/svg_play</description></item><item><title>rktpi</title><link>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://thetanil.github.io/rktpi/post/rktpi/</guid><description>What it is A platform for web apps running on YOUR Pi, with YOUR Data, accessible from YOUR phone.
Your data in your home. Your safe space near the Internet.
Features A guard computer for your phone A transformer of documents An internet filtered of garbage A path out of the cloud Keep your own email, back it up EZ UX - just for you ads be damned Extremely opinionated to favor accessibility and UX performance No JS, just enough CSS to unify browsers, there is no ad network No colors, user theme-able viewer Gemini with markdown and pictures Target 3G full page renders under 200ms (not including images) Has to may may but with SVG they can be big think HighQualityGifs you see them when they are cached already comments about a content item are found in matrix via #content_id The Questions Rocket Pi is an attempt to answer the following questions:</description></item></channel></rss>